adcombo.com 2019-03-26

# Privacy policy

## Personal data protection

Your personal data are protected at all stages: entering, transmitting and processing your information.

## The disclosure of personal data and their transfer to third parties

Your personal data may be disclosed by us only if required in following cases : (a) to ensure compliance with the legal requirements or to comply with legal process in our regard; (b) to protect and defend our rights or property, (c) to take urgent measures to ensure the personal safety of our employees or consumers and services they provide, as well as for public safety. Personal information collected by us during your registration may be transferred to third parties and organizations, which are our partner companies to improve the quality of services provided. This information will not be used for any purposes other than those listed above. The email address you provided during the registration can be used to send you messages or notification of changes related to your order, and messages to inform you of the company's events and updates, as well as important information about new products, services, etc. You can unsubscribe to these e-mail notifications.

## The use of «cookies»

When a user visits a website a short text called «cookies» is sent to his computer (if the user ‘s browser allows the reception of such files). If the user has already visited this website, the «cookies» file is read from the computer. One of the uses of «cookies» is the collection of visit statistics. This data helps determine what information sent by the customers is of special interest to them. These data are collected in an aggregated form and never match the personal data of users

Third parties, including Google, display our ads on various websites. They use «cookies» to show ads based on previous visits by the user of our website and their interest recorded by the browsers. The users can prohibit the use of «cookies» by Google. To do this, visit a dedicated Google page at: [http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/](https://www.google.com/privacy/ads/)

## Changes to the privacy statement

Privacy Statement is supposed to be updated periodically. The date of the previous update, indicated at the beginning of the document will be thus changed. Announcements of the amendments in this statement will be posted in a visible area of our websites.

## Thank you for your interest in our system!

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.
